

# Iryna Loushkina

FRONTED DEVELOPER

#### **Details**

Hilversum, Netherlands +31 6 12 96 30 71 iloushkina@gmail.com

#### Links

Linkedin

GitHub

CodePen

CV web page

### Skills

HTML/CSS (SCSS)

JavaScript

BEM methodology

React

Redux

Git/GitHub

npm

Webpack

Adobe Photoshop

### Languages

English

Ukrainian | Russian

Dutch

# Hobbies

Running Cycling

Traveling Cooking

# **Profile**

7+ years experience in many different projects, starting from sales/account management, implementation online booking tools to managing people.

I am a self-taught Frontend Developer. My technology stack is HTML5, CSS3 (SCSS), JavaScript(ES6), React, Redux, Git/GitHub, npm, Webpack, and the BEM methodology. I keep developing my skills.

You are more than welcome to visit my portfolio webpage following the link https://iloush.github.io/irina\_loushkina\_cv/

# **Employment History**

Junior Frontend Developer, Hilversum, Netherlands

FEBRUARY 2020

- Semantic, cross-browser, adaptive, and responsive development of landing pages.
- Familiar with Developer Tools and Version Control system (Git, GitHub).

Tech stack:

HTML5 CSS3 (SCSS) BEM methodology

JavaScript React/Redux jQuery
npm Webpack AJAX

### 3D Modelling and Design, Kiev, Ukraine

JULY 2018 - DECEMBER 2019

### Account Manager, Booking.com, Kiev, Ukraine

JULY 2017 - JUNE 2018

Senior Account Manager, American Express Global Business Travel, Kiev, Ukraine

NOVEMBER 2015 - JULY 2017

Account Manager, American Express Global Business Travel, Kiev, Ukraine

APRIL 2014 – NOVEMBER 2015

# Flight Attendant, Ukraine International Airlines, Kiev, Ukraine

APRIL 2011 - JANUARY 2014

# **Education**

Bachelor degree of Foreign Economic Activity Management, National Aviation University, Kiev, Ukraine

SEPTEMBER 2007 - MAY 2011

# **Courses**

Full JavaScript + React course, Udemy

MAY 2020 - PRESENT

Business Analysis Essentials based on BABOK (3.0), IIBA, Kiev, Ukraine

JULY 2018 - JULY 2018

